<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fpdoc-descriptions>
  <package name="ghORM Framework">
    <module name="ghORM">
      <short>Object Relational Mapping unit built on top of Greyhound project</short>
      <descr>The idea is to automate saving and loading of published properties. Note that the API is not yet stable, it might change in the future without notice</descr>
      <element name="TModel">
        <short>Base class for all ghORM models</short>
        <descr>All models should inherit from this class and implement the abstract methods and create the respective <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TORM"/> for the CRUD-er.</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.FID">
        <short>Database ID for this model's object</short>
        <descr>Read-only by design, as one should not alter this. Take whatever value obtained from the <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TORM"/> instance instead.</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.GetTableName">
        <short>Override this method to give a database table name for this model</short>
        <descr>Other methods accepting TghSQLTable parameter shall receive an instance of this table</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.Validate">
        <short>Override this method to implement automatic validation when saving an object (insert/update) through <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TORM"/> instance</short>
        <errors>Automatic validation isn't yet implemented, but it shall be soon</errors>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.LoadFromTable">
        <short>Override this method to assign object's properties from given table instance</short>
        <descr>The table instance already points to respective row in the table, so you just have to assign the values to properties such as:
<p><code>FField := ATable['column-name'].AsString;
</code></p>
        </descr>
        <errors>If you access non-existing column, an exception will be generated</errors>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.SaveToTable">
        <short>Override this method to assign table instance columns with current object's properties</short>
        <descr>The table instance already points to respective row in the table, so you just have to assign the values to properties such as:
<p><code>ATable['column-name'].AsString := FField;
</code></p>
        </descr>
        <errors>If you access non-existing column, an exception will be generated</errors>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.LoadRelationships">
        <short>Override this method to load actual instances of linked tables</short>
        <descr>By default, when getting an object from <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TORM"/> instance, the linked objects from table relationships are not loaded. This is to prevent stack overflow in case of M-N relationship. This method will be called automatically when calling <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TORM.ResolveLinks"/>.</descr>
        <errors>If you access non-existing link, an exception will be generated</errors>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.LoadFromTable.ATable">
        <short>Table instance resembling the current object</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.SaveToTable.ATable">
        <short>Table instance resembling the current object</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.SaveRelationships">
        <short>Override this method to load actual instances of linked tables</short>
        <descr>In case of an insert operation, the object doesn't have an ID yet. So we can't save the object and relationships in one go. This method is supposed to save the relationships and will be automatically called upon insert/update. The <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TORM"/> instance will take care of the saving order (the object first, retrieve its ID and use it to save the relationships).</descr>
        <errors>If you access non-existing link, an exception will be generated</errors>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.LoadRelationships.ALinks">
        <short>List of tables linked to this model</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.SaveRelationships.ALinks">
        <short>List of tables linked to this model</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TModel.ID">
        <short>Property access for the protected <link id="#ghormpkg.ghorm.TModel.FID"/> field</short>
      </element>
    </module>
  </package>
</fpdoc-descriptions>
